[{"answer": "The most --", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "What's the question?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Do you really think Warren Buffet need as much attention from the government as the most vulnerable?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "You know, I think there's two things at play here.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Why are so few members of his own party properly in love with Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think anybody could come to the conclusion he doesn't want it.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Why doesn't he look like he wants this more?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "I would not be called the reserved type, right?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "No, I don't accept the criticism.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Do you accept any of that criticism of the way he's being perceived?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, well, whoa.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "But the fact is, what's the difference?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, the difference is that many people in the Republican Party actually think the last thing he is is severely conservative.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "What's the difference?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "I think you have to look at the -- at the sum of someone's record.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "And that comes back to my thing at the start about the battle for the heart and soul of the party, is which way is the party instinctively now going to go?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "One, I think he's got integrity.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "What are the characteristics of him that are not getting over at the moment that you see when you speak to him privately that persuaded you to put your reputation behind him?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "No, I'm really not.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "You're not feeling the surge?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I won't be.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "But if you were being critical of him in the campaign?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Not publicly.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "None that I'm telling you.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "So what suggestions have you already made to him that you could now repeat to me?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "It's going to come from inside him.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "What have we not seen so far?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I sure do.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Do you care about the poor, Governor?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I don't think it's my obligation to characterize the economy as a fiasco.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "So this has to be a concern for the Republicans as they go into the proper election battle, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Listen, you know, I've got to tell you the truth, I didn't spend a lot of time thinking about it because what I was doing at the time --", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Did you approve, instinctively, yourself, of the bailout of the auto industry?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, yes, but -- I mean, you know, I actually try to give things more thought than just three or four seconds before I give you an opinion.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "But now that I've asked you to think about it?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Right now, since you just asked me, and that was the context within which you put it.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "You've only given it three or four seconds thought?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Well, listen, as I just told you, I haven't spent a lot of time thinking about it.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "But what do you think?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "What I have is, what I have is a view of what's happening here in this state because that's my job.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "You don't have a view of the bailout of the American auto industry?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "-- of education.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Does he deserve it for that?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Sure it is.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Is it complex?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Sure it is.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Well, my view is that the government should have as little involvement in the private sector as it possibly can.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "What is your view ideologically of bailouts?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "I'm pleased people are working.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Are you pleased it's worked?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Sure it is.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Is it not a debate that's worth having, though?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, I think what would be a good thing is for us to allow the people, the shareholders and the executives of those companies, to make their decisions.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Wouldn't that be a good thing?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "All I could tell you is what I do.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Because whichever you play that clip, even if you play every single word, and you take him exactly on the context you wanted it to sound like, he's still prioritizing middle class Americans in his head over the poor, isn't it?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "I -- the most vulnerable --", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "What's the question?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Do you really think Warren Buffet needs as much attention from the government as the most vulnerable?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "I got the question right.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "What's the answer?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, Warren Buffet doesn't live in New Jersey --", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "You know, is it right that, taking your argument to its natural conclusion that Warren Buffet is as much in your head for his economic situation as the poorest person in New Jersey?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "I don't know the answer to that question.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "How many billionaires are there in New Jersey?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "I -- really, I have not a clue.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Roughly?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Everybody will get 10 percent.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "But are all the billionaires in New Jersey, under this plan, going to get 10 percent income tax reduction?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Wait a second.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "But are you worried you're -- you're beginning to be slightly out of touch, given that seven states now, I think, have legalized gay marriage, Washington being the latest, given that others are likely to follow?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Well, it would have been in step with 50 of the states, but now it's only 43.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "So, you're suggesting that because my position is in step with 43 of the 50 states, that proves I'm out of step?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "I won't compromise my principles for politics.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Yes, but at what stage does it become politically strange?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "No, not my principles.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Ever?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I would not compromise my principles for politics.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "You would never change your mind about this?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Some, yes.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Do you get flak from gay friends for this?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "We have a robust conversation about why I have the position I have and they have the position they have.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "What do they say to you?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Do they -- do they accuse you directly of being bigoted?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Would they have a right to?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "It's not a bigoted position?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Listen, I don't have -- I don't have any problem with people using contraception.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Again, I guess because you're a Catholic, you would be opposed to it?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "ORGAN: It's as simple as that?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "I think it's a distraction and I think -- and I think that, you know, while it's a very important issue and that there are people who feel fiercely on both sides of the question of ObamaCare, not on contraception, although there is some debate about that as well.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What do you think about the whole debate that came out recently?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Well, listen, you know, that's the law of the state and the legislature has put it in effect long before I came here and it's my job to enforce the law.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Are you personally in favor of that?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I think the American people should be thinking about the extraordinary gifts that this country makes available to them, of opportunity, of the ability to be able to live where you want to live, to pick the career you want to pick, and to really be restricted in this country, still today, only by what your own ambition and your willingness to work hard and to strive for.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "What do Americans need to be thinking about?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Only in America.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "That's the American Dream at its best, isn't it?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Yes, I would.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "You would accept that?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Make the difficult decisions without regard to anything other than what you think is in the best interests of the state.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "How could that apply successfully, in your view, to America?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "In political corruption, we won 130 cases without a defeat.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "You fought 130 case?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "You never lost?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Have you ever lost an election?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "A few.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "How many?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Always to be yourself and not to get -- listen to people in your ear, the consultants and the others who try to tack you and turn you and color you, but to be yourself, because then you have no regrets.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "What did you learn about yourself from the defeats?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I don't think the two are mutually exclusive.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Can you be true to yourself completely as president or is the job simply too, now, predicated on having to deals all the time with the opposition to get anything done?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "I don't think you can assume it, because, you know, only God knows what life brings you.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Can we assume that at some stage, you might run?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "I -- no.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "It's not your bag, is it, to do that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Can I see the rest of the statehouse?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "I'm trying to be in charge, and to -- to give off the minute I walk through this door, to give all of the people who will be sitting here, the people of the gallery, the sense that I'm in charge.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "What was that -- what's the demeanor you're trying to create as you march in?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "It's like a mini senate, isn't it?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "What it --", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "When you're standing there doing your thing -- I mean, this looks like the senate to me -- when you're standing there doing your thing, you must -- your mind must occasionally flash forward to a slightly bigger stage, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "Yes, it's about accomplishments, yes.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "I mean, that is really what being a politician is all about, isn't it?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "listen, yes, you are.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 743, "question": "You have lost quite a little weight since I last saw you?", "qSentId": 742}, {"answer": "You know, I'm intermittently on a mission on this stuff.", "docId": "120225pmt", "aSentId": 748, "question": "You're now on a bit of a mission?", "qSentId": 747}]